#### Personal Details

# Carlos Reta Domínguez Carrer Sant Joaquim 9E, 08800 Vilanova i la Geltrú 650303697 - juanki114@gmail.com Spanish – English

## Summary

Software Engineer specialized in front technologies, analysis, design, and development of JavaScript-based applications. Solid, design patterns and Unit testing. Focused on good design, clean code, best practices, and performance. Currently working in Angular apps. UX capabilities.

### **Formation**

Universitat Pompeu Fabra – Computer Science Engineer 2002 – 2007

# **Experience**

## Front-end Architect

## **CREALOGIX Group · Full-time**

## Aug 2020 - Present · 2 yrs 11 mos

- Participation in the architecture FE team in decision-making.
- Development, enhancement, and maintenance of the current UXF Framework libraries.
- Resolution of UXF customer issues
- Framework documentation
- New features to enhance development speeds (agile builder tools)
- Development of product-oriented applications (Builder, Design Studio, Playground)
- Technical support to projects ensuring the correct application of the best practices proposed by architecture.
- Code audits
- POC seeking to implement and innovate the best solutions for UXF
- Including investigations to deliver customer-requested features, for example, Micro frontends
- Investigation in up-to-date technology such as tools used by the community learned from conferences and Angular or community releases (Allows to make UXF and projects better and more agile).
- UXF training internally and to customers.
- UXF Training
- Conducting workshops or material aimed at helping the improvement of the company's developers.
- UXF Projects Architecture definitions
- Complete the testing cycle of UXF libraries and applications.

• Guidelines definition, standards, DevOps integration workflow definition for different types of teams (Externals, internals, multi squad, project, product)

#### Front-end Leader

## Alpega

## 2014 - 2020

- Analysis and development of front-end applications.
- Focused on the component architecture, full code testing, and helping with UI and UX when needed.
- Expert in using technologies such as Angular, Typescript, Redux, Jasmine, REST Services, CSS3, HTML5, Git, Jenkins, Docker, and AWS

## Software engineer

## HP

## 2007 - 2014

- Java applications and health care consultant.
- Customization of the HP health application (HCIS).
- Development and implementation of two new modules of the application for Sabadell Hospital: Outpatient and Day Hospital.
- Coordination of the corrective maintenance area of the hospital.
- Analysis of incoming incidents and distribution among the different people in the team.
- Coordination of the team and resolution of the most complex incidents.

## **Technologies**

- Angular, Typescript, NGRX, RXJS, Redux
- Unit Testing: Jasmine, Karma, Jest
- E2e Testing: Cypress, Webdriver.io